that a very
good morning friends welcome back
to you on bar question oy drive safe mission
possible addiction * varna kasana ank with another
set of questions this is the 14th day of
togetherness and we are on the road safety mission
supervisor come together and we know how to make
indian roads safe mode and here is the
question on screen as you can see and i
screen the question about you love you are
driving and car late in the night sadan live
encounter for the role you will now be driving at night very
late kar rahe hain definitely you saw that half the road par jo hai is shocked so that situation
me aap kya karega kanjar driver headlights
on aap par device on kar kar rahenge aur ya pulverizer side and turn on web link words
aap par sa
aapne alag aakhir aur aapne bhring usko on kar denge continue drive 10,000 lights on aap drive kar rahenge aur 1000 likes ko kar kar kar kar kar denge continue drive
10,000 lights on
aap drive kar rahenge aur 1000 likes ko kar kar kar kar kar denge
Worshipable foggy
area 0 Then we will drive quickly and at high speed
so that you
can crush this clear, so stay with us and you
can also be a part of this entire work,
this is definitely a city mission to save your form
and we would request you not to
join alone but with your family, your friends, your loved ones so that you have a chance to
win a gift, so now tell us what will happen to you
because such users do not feel like
in winters when we are on the highway, there is a lot of
tension, such situations have been seen many times that
fog comes, then
these people do not understand what to do at that
time, so tell us that you
complete the situation and if your answer is correct
then you have a chance to
win a very exciting gift, Android user
Refix, right now this is the first question of
the day for questions raw left perpendicular, we
mean a one by one after two, today you have 2
hours to answer this question
For and raw after that our names will come out, others will
join you and will
talk to you in detail and will bring new
questions, you can participate in that too, you
heard it right, you
can participate in all the five questions,
632 have been added on daily basis, this campaign is for instability
and of everyone you can
benefit * mode to go, so today pay a little attention, more
days are left for you to join us, we will
request you to join as many as possible
and
be a part of this entire campaign, now the
question which is visible on the screen in Dekh sakte is you are
driving your car late in the night always
encounter for golden rule you will continue to deal with
head light on those people other side
and can you now wrinkles connected amount 1000
likes on drive fast worship forgive a
Rasool so what will you do, at that time you will keep
typing by turning on your head light
or by putting the right side and you will turn on your Brinks,
now keep driving  By turning on your
Izzat light or you will
press it quickly so that
you can cross that foggy area, so tell
us what will be your answer, these small
things, this is our entire campaign of Delhi Vidhan Sabha,
secondly regarding road safety, this is
our entire mission, on which one
road safety features want you and more, in
Lovevanshi to be a relationship, you
can join it every day and by joining with us,
you can get the opportunity to
hide many such gifts, let us tell you on
daily basis, how many people die
on the road and no one comes to save them
and sir, due to small negligence,
we get the same thing, we have to
remove that small negligence,
if the day we will be able to do that, then
which SIM will you bring, that we should
not make these small mistakes because it is for the
safety of our SIM and the people associated with us, only then we will be able to
make our day safe and safe, so come, I
request you please join hands together
because this thing is a big challenge
This will not happen with the death of one person, from f4
we will all together read to script that
why will you call us ours,
you are using our text every day or you
are connected to it, so that is why we
request you that please join
us and be a part of this entire campaign, so for the
last time I have a question for you
on Duggar driving hona car
let in the night Sadan Duma encounter of
wonder rule politics driver light on pull and
earth side and torn and now wrinkles
scars policy driver light on drive
fast to pass the furious one please connect
with dance and do not insult to answer this
question stresses stay healthy stay tuned vanished into it
otherwise Kasana will be will join
ignorance with any specific
questions and raw mango friends welcome and join with you
IS with another set of
questions will be back with any other city's
questions and please now Hari begins with
his full camp in it's an a team  of every
221 be a part of this thank you so much oo
happened